Today we just drink together.
Fun.
It's fun.
Because you still have the last of your work?
Today.
Well, have a lot of drinks.
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, Mom.
Does your mom have the day off yet?
I don't have time off.
No, she doesn't.
What are you doing? Schedule.
My schedule is a little tight.
We've been on location all day, and we've been running and moving around.
You've been busy, huh?
Yes, we are.
But you two are pretty busy too, so I can't say that.
Weren't you chosen as the face of the year?
Yeah.
They did.
I think you were the biggest breakout hit last year. My mom.
Yes, ma'am.
My reward for being the best.
She threw me a polly-pooh.
She gave me a compliment.
Oh, Mom, you look great today.
I love it.
I don't like it.
He's throwing me around like I'm a messy 2x3.
Nice shell.
It's good to eat.
Thanks, me.
I'm going to be in a weird TV show called "I'm a Heartbeat" and they're going to sing a song as a unit and it's a very silly song. That's weird.
The same?
Yeah.
You're there?
This Yaniksa guy's going on MSTV?
Don't say "yaniksa.
Smells good.
What?
That's a lot.
You only get to do this once in your life.
I'm on MTV, too.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, why?
I have my own show.
I'm doing a collaboration for it.
I'm going to be dancing the Volute Dance on M STAR.
Was it? Oh, I was doing this.
What are you doing here?
I've never been to a bar.
But Keir's gonna be there, and he likes to drink.
Let's go.
You want to take Ano there?
There's a Japanese restaurant we'll definitely go to.
A Japanese restaurant?
It's really good.
It's run by a mom and a dad.
They're good, too.
This is Hiko Lohi.
He's got a really nice voice.
It's been a long time, Dad.
You're on TV...
He brought me here today.
I've seen her. - You have?
You like kueh?
There's kuehoe in the casserole.
Kue?
I don't know.
Yose-nabe first.
Let's start with Yose-nabe.
Who?
You look like him.
I'm more than Mr. Korokke.
We look so much alike, really.
Like this? It's really like this?
We look so much alike.
I usually drink there.
They always ask me about Kueh.
What do you mean, "kueh"?
There's kueh in it today.
And chestnut chips.
I cut them up into little pieces.
They're good.
Let's go grab a bite.
I'd like to go there.
I didn't know you liked to drink.
Let's go.
That's surprising... the gap between us.
That's true.
I'd think you'd say you don't like that kind of party.
But you don't like gatherings?
I've been to a few big ones, and I just couldn't handle it.
It was awful.
That's true.
There are some weird artists.
I don't know.
There are a lot of artists.
It's a little bit harsh.
What's it like?
How many people are there?
I'm just saying, I have a friend who's in it.
I have a friend who's a wancer.
It's like a big, famous artist.
They're like two sides of the same coin.
They have their own songs that they sing.
Is there really such a thing?
Yes, it does.
I've already left.
That's tough.
Can I just ask your name?
I think I might like it.
Is this the party that the artist from the "Cirque du Soleil" is having?
Yeah. - Oh, I don't like them at all.
Oh, I don't like them at all.
I love Southern music.
If Kuwata-san was talking about that kind of party...
I know, we don't have them often, but sometimes they happen.
Anmika's birthday party was amazing at Onlins.
That's how it was.
Yes, yes. But even then, it was like I was the only comedian.
And then there were all kinds of models.
People from different industries.
Yes, there was a big projection outside with all the celebrities.
And everyone was watching the miracle of Anmika and her husband.
Wow.
That's amazing.
Bright.
So happy.
Well, well, well. I'll be on my own.
Whew!
You're right.
I don't have one of those.
Oh, yeah, Ammika's gonna have to blend in a little bit.
You know, sometimes we have parties like that.
I was thinking that last year.
Nasunaka-san and Anmika-san said they'd have a drink.
What? Anmika and Nasunaka?
Anmika's been saying she liked Nasunaka-san since before he got his big break.
She's said in various places that she liked you.
She said in various places that she liked that umbrella after Nasunaka-san got her big break.
Then I said I was happy for you and we were going to have a drink, and I left Fluffy behind and got together with Fuwa-chan, Fuwa, Nasunaka and Ammika because it was near Ammika's birthday.
I was so happy to see Ammika's Happy Birthday plate at that time, and I was like, "Wow, that's great," and I was like, "Five people, Nasunaka, Huwa, Ammika, and Hikorohee.
Three-fifths of them are from Kotake Entertainment.
There was no entertainment hall.
That's a relief!
It's rare to see such a high concentration of Kotake.
There wasn't.
I've never seen an arts center like that.
I'm sure they'll call Hiko Lohi, though.
I'm sure he'll be invited.
No, no, no. He's not good at drinking.
I mean, I've seen what you're capable of, Hatake.
He's a great drinker.
What do you mean, "good at drinking"?
He's a good drinker. I'm sure of it.
You know?
Yes, he does.
As a comedian, of course.
But...
But there's also the power of the drinking party.
When I was a college student, I was happy with the power of the drinking game.
I don't mean how much you drink.
I mean the way you talk to all the people in the bar
I was talking to all the people in the bar.
And talking about yourself, too.
And talking about yourself and being a funny guy.
But I don't really know how to drink anymore.
I just like to drink.
What the hell is your drinking ability?
No, I'm serious.
I'm sure you're good at drinking.
I'm sure there's cooperation too.
DAIGO also has the ability to get drunk.
I see.
He's just a guy who drinks and adapts to the drinking situation, and he likes people.
I don't feel like I can convey my strengths at such places because I'm not good at drinking anymore, and I don't think I'd enjoy it.
I don't think I'd enjoy going to a place like that because I don't think I'd be able to convey my qualities.
You know, when you're recording a show and everyone's talking about something and you're like, "Wow!
You know, like when you say, "Well, you know...
You're probably not the type of person I'd like to be.
Well, you know...
I don't think she'll reject you.
It's just a line.
That's your charm.
At a bar, there's a lot of that kind of thing going on.
So she'll say, "I'm...
And then you go in?
That's right.
I can't go in there.
Well, I was in a drinking party with Hiko Lohi.
I don't know... I don't know... I don't know...
No, no, no, no, I think it's a drinking party.
It's like we're talking to Tok Tok Tok.
What kind of drinking party is that?
Like it's my club.
Something about shocking people
It's like...
What's with this taiyaki?
What's with the pillar version?
I'm like, "What's going on?
Well, if they didn't lift him up, then...
Then he's not good enough.
If he's not being lifted up, then he's not the most talented.
If he's not being lifted up, he's not the most talented.
That's just part of being a hikikorohei. It's better that way.
That's better.
That's why we don't have any stories like that.
You know...
And the song... they want you to sing.
What? Karaoke?
We have karaoke.
What do you want? Something for everyone.
Can you sing "Marigold"?
Yes, I can.
Can you sing the chorus?
The wind is a little strong.
The wind's a little too strong.
I like the way you look at me so seriously... but I don't know most of the words.
Pretend to feel sorry for me
Let's pretend you're not. Let's pretend you're not.
Here you go.
Now?
I'm happy that you're shining right in front of me like a marigold swaying in everyone's hat.
Ayama, the sky is still blue in summer
the love of that day that made me smile and say I missed it
Don't leave me again, you who stares at me with eyes that look like they're about to cry
Gentleness like a cloud holding you tight all the time
Hug, hug, hug you
Woo
All of my true feelings
I'm not strong enough to let it out
Waiit na show
But no wonder
No, not at all.
Who's that girl? I don't know... someone who looks like her, but pretends not to.
I don't think so.
Who is she?
He's always been in the back of my eyes.
Silhouette in the back of my eyes
I love you.
Soft
Our skin against each other
A little cold air
Bite down on the green raccoon biting down on the green raccoon biting down on the green raccoon biting down on the green raccoon biting down on the green raccoon
I'll name the balloon of the green raccoon
I'll give you a name... you're lucky
I love you
No, no, no, no, he's a spin artist, so maybe it's over, but you tell me, Tetsuya...
You tell him, Tetsuya.
No, it was fun.
It was fun.
His impersonation of Seiya was too similar.
I was joking about playing the piano during the chorus.
That was Ucchan's impersonation of Pocket Biscuit.
Can you put that in there for a second?
You were a little confused, weren't you? Yes, I was.
Yes, yes, yes.
Grandpa.
He was doing that Uchimura thing when I was a beginner.
You're the old man with the red nose, right?
The red wind...
Then he was in on it.
Thank you for watching.